[Music] I'm
so bored today that my
boredom knows no bounds.
I've crossed all the boundaries of boredom.
And this impossible disaster, my sister, is
studying. Even slaps have turned into flowers
today. But you can say anything, but I won't let you
eat or drink. Then I take a magical hug and move away.
He's a very rude buffalo.
And then I'm eating spinach with great ease.
Then a smart and nice guy comes along. "Yes, I
know how to come, it's a little casual,
brother, I'm very hungry. My stomach is saying, '
Gud, good brother, I want to build my body, give me juice.'
Ignoring their demands, we end up destroying our health.
After that, I look on TikTok and
bring it home. Hello, sorry, Payal, and
I ask the icy bear for a
cup of tea, but my request is rejected.
Actually, it's something like this: I ca
n't make tea. Good boy, he
makes very good tea. Thank you so much. The
tea is really good."  I
see a very strange incident happening here and when I
protest against it, I myself get caught
in that incident. What is this goon doing? I will
leave the bird in the house and come back. After
reaching home, I narrate the entire incident to my sister.